<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>1</ID>
    <Text>SOLANUM: That's incredible! The main systems work despite the damage. I'm sure I can handle this.</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>2</ID>
    <ParentID>1</ParentID>
    <Text>SOLANUM: This wall shows incoming messages from other Nomai clans. It may be strange, but they believe Escall's Vessel Disappearance was a myth.</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>3</ID>
    <ParentID>2</ParentID>
    <Text>SOLANUM: It's incredible <![CDATA[<color=orange>the Vessel</color>]]> can receive these messages here in <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Dark Bramble</color>]]>. Perhaps I can trace them back...</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>4</ID>
    <ParentID>3</ParentID>
    <Text>SOLANUM: A Nomai, Canna, mentions a safe place called <![CDATA[<color=orange>«Blackrock»</color>]]> system, somewhere in the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Gloaming Galaxy</color>]]>.</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>5</ID>
    <ParentID>4</ParentID>
    <Text>SOLANUM: The ship has the message source's coordinates! I can put it up on the display, which must be somewhere. Please find it. If we decide to warp, we need the warp core from <![CDATA[<color=orange> Ash Twin Project</color>]]>. The original core is irreparably damaged. </Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>6</ID>
    <ParentID>5</ParentID>
    <Text>SOLANUM: Thinking of such a possibility is exciting. But I do not fear this. In fact, after all that has happened, I have no fear at all. These are simply the laws by which the universe lives.</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>7</ID>
    <ParentID>6</ParentID>
    <Text>SOLANUM: Two conscious observers starting a journey towards destiny. I can feel the uncertainty grow enormously. It hasn't felt this strong since I left the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon</color>]]>.</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>8</ID>
    <ParentID>7</ParentID>
    <Text>SOLANUM: There will be no turning back. I am ready for whatever is next, friend. The decision is yours.</Text>
  </TextBlock> 
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>SOLANUM_ON_DB</FactID>
      <Condition>1</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>SOLANUM_DB_VESSEL</FactID>
      <Condition>1</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>SOLANUM_DB_RECORDER</FactID>
      <Condition>8</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>IS_HOLOGRAM_CHANGED</FactID>
      <Condition>8</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>