<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
  <ID>TIMBER_HEARTH</ID>

  <Entry>
    <ID>SOLANUM_TH</ID>
    <Name>Solanum on Timber Hearth</Name>

    <Curiosity>THE_VISION_CURIOSITY</Curiosity>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>SOLANUM_RUMOR_TH</ID>
      <SourceID>THE_VISION_ENTRY</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Is Solanum on Timber Hearth?</RumorName>
      <Text>Solanum is asking to find her. Maybe I should start from Timber Hearth since it's nearby?</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>SOLANUM_TH</ID>
      <Text>Solanum somehow appeared on Timber Hearth near the Village. It seems like she's observing the Hearthians.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>SOLANUM_TH_RECORDER</ID>
      <Text>According to her recorder, she just thought of Timber Hearth and appeared there. That could be explainable with my new Quantum Rule. Solanum told me about the Sun Station, she apologized, but that's ok. Solanum also would like to know more about the Probe Tracking Module inside Giant's Deep.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <Entry>
      <ID>NEW_QUANTUM_RULE</ID>
      <Name>New quantum rule</Name>
      <Curiosity>THE_VISION_CURIOSITY</Curiosity>

      <RumorFact>
        <ID>WHAT_IS_NEW_QR</ID>
        <RumorName>New quantum rule?</RumorName>
        <Text>I've discovered strange frequency called Quantum Consciousness.</Text>
      </RumorFact>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>NEW_QUANTUM_RULE_QC</ID>
        <Text>This could be a new quantum rule or an quantum exception. My theory is if a conscious observer is aware of his quantum properties, they acquire Quantum Consciousness. Solanum probably got this knowledge from my vision.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>NEW_QUANTUM_RULE_QC_SIGNAL</ID>
        <Text>Quantum Consciousness has a strong recognizable signal and it sounds similar to the Quantum Fluctuations. In fact, the signal is so much stronger that it can be heard even without signalscope.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>NEW_QUANTUM_RULE_QC_PARTICLES</ID>
        <Text>Another noticable thing about Quantum Consciousness - particles near the head. By the way, seems like other quantum rules are not working with Quantum Consciousness.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>NEW_QUANTUM_RULE_QC_ABILITY</ID>
        <Text>Something with Quantum Consciousness somehow has the ability to exist in a multiple places at the same time. Solanum declares that they can only think about the certain location and appear there. Hypothesis: they can appear only in known places.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>

  </Entry>
</AstroObjectEntry>