<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
  <ID>TIMBER_HEARTH</ID>

  <Entry>
    <ID>SOLANUM_TH</ID>
    <Name>Solanum on Timber Hearth</Name>

    <Curiosity>THE_VISION_CURIOSITY</Curiosity>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>SOLANUM_RUMOR_TH</ID>
      <SourceID>THE_VISION_ENTRY</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Is Solanum on Timber Hearth?</RumorName>
      <Text>Solanum's message was interrupted when she mentioned Timber Hearth. Maybe she is there?</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>SOLANUM_TH</ID>
      <Text>Solanum somehow appeared on Timber Hearth near the Village. It seems like she is observing the Hearthians.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>SOLANUM_TH_RECORDER</ID>
      <Text>According to her recorder, she just thought of Timber Hearth and appeared there. That could be explainable with my new Quantum Rule. Solanum told me about the Sun Station, she apologized, but that's ok. Solanum would also like to know more about the Probe Tracking Module inside Giant's Deep.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <Entry>
      <ID>NEW_QUANTUM_RULE</ID>
      <Name>Quantum Consciousness</Name>
      <Curiosity>THE_VISION_CURIOSITY</Curiosity>

      <RumorFact>
        <ID>WHAT_IS_NEW_QR</ID>
        <RumorName>New quantum frequency?</RumorName>
        <Text>I've discovered strange frequency called Quantum Consciousness.</Text>
      </RumorFact>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>NEW_QUANTUM_RULE_QC</ID>
        <Text>This could be a new quantum rule or an quantum exception. My theory is that if an observer is aware of its quantum properties, it acquire Quantum Consciousness. Solanum probably got this knowledge from my vision.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>NEW_QUANTUM_RULE_QC_SIGNAL</ID>
        <Text>Quantum Consciousness has a strong recognizable signal and it sounds similar to the Quantum Fluctuations. In fact, the signal is very strong. It can be heard even without signalscope.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>NEW_QUANTUM_RULE_QC_PARTICLES</ID>
        <Text>Another noticable thing about Quantum Consciousness - particles near the head. By the way, seems like other quantum rules are not working with Quantum Consciousness.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>NEW_QUANTUM_RULE_QC_ABILITY</ID>
        <Text>Quantum Consciousness somehow has the ability to exist in a multiple places at the same time. According to Solanum, she is only capable of appearing at certain locations by thinking about them. Hypothesis: she can appear only in known places.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>

  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>ERNESTO_ENTRY</ID>
    <Name>Where is Ernesto?</Name>

    <Curiosity>ERNESTO_CURIOSITY</Curiosity>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>ERNESTO_RUMOR</ID>
      <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Where is Ernesto?</RumorName>
      <Text>Seriously, how could an anglerfish just disappear?</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>ERNESTO_ENTRY</ID>
      <Text>Hornfels said that anglerfish «Ernesto» disappeared from exhibit.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>ERNESTO_FOUND</ID>
    <Name>Ernesto found</Name>

    <Curiosity>ERNESTO_CURIOSITY</Curiosity>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>ERNESTO_FOUND_RUMOR</ID>
      <SourceID>ERNESTO_ENTRY</SourceID>
      <RumorName>I found Ernesto</RumorName>
      <Text>Where is Ernesto?</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>ERNESTO_FOUND_FACT</ID>
      <Text>I found Slate with Ernesto. He's cooking him on campfire.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>ERNESTO_POOR_ERNESTO</ID>
      <Text>Slate is just fed up with marshmallow, that's why he decided to cook Ernesto. He said it will be ready in 30 minutes. Intervention isn't required because the loop will reset before that happens.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

</AstroObjectEntry>